

Profile

A highly skilled Quality Assurance Engineer with 2 years of experience in designing effective test cases from system requirements and creating automated tests, including unit and performance tests.

I am adept at collaborating with development teams to diagnose and resolve issues and bugs, and I possess strong analytical skills that enable me to plan tests efficiently. Additionally, I have experience of leading QA team and ensuring that all testing activities are completed on time and to the highest standards.

Contact

PHONE:

+251905518244

LinkedIn:

Atsedemariam Bizuneh | LinkedIn

EMAIL: latseden@gmail.com

Hobbies

- Watching videos or reading topics about recent topics of technologies.
- Reading books.
- Discussing with friends on a certain topic.

Language

- Amharic native
- English very good
- Ge'ez good

Atsedemariam Bizuneh

QA Engineer

Education

Bahirdar University (Sept 2017 – Sept 2021)

Software Engineering

GPA - 3.84

I studied software design, development, testing, and maintenance. I gained comprehensive knowledge and was a team leader throughout my studies. My final project ranked among the top five in my faculty.

Bahirdar University (Oct 2018 – Aug. 2022)

Management

GPA - 3.6

I studied team management, project management, communication, and other essential subjects to enhance my skills and knowledge.

Work Experience

Tern systems (Iceland) - QAE

January 2022 - present

Responsible for ensuring that the air traffic control system (ATC) developed by the company meet the highest quality standards. I create and execute test cases to identify any issues or defects in the software. Working closely with the development team, I collaborate to resolve any issues.

Poshak consultancy plc. - Software Developer

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Software development with vue is.

Projects (personal)

- Face recognition system python
- Hospital management system c++
- Property management system laravel, sql
- Ethio-tour website php, html, css and sql
- Games (snake, basketball, code block, flappy bird) unity c#

Skills

